Based on our makeup and character relationships,
let's design the positioning for a poster.
We design it ourselves?
Alright.
Understood. Let's just explain the character relationships.
That's the idea.
Character relationships...
I think it goes like this.
This Fifth Uncle is definitely the oldest.
Fifth Uncle is the oldest, obviously.
His positioning is fine.
No.
I'm two years older than Fifth Uncle.
Three years older.
She's older than me.
Sister-in-law is older than me.
I'm the sister-in-law.
I'm Eldest Sister-in-law.
Right, right, right.
Highest seniority.
Alright.
Then you sit, sister-in-law.
Sister-in-law isn't sitting yet.
Because sister-in-law's illusion tights look a bit thick.
Then our oldest brother will sit first.
Right?
Oldest brother.
Sit.
Oldest brother sitting is fine, right?
Sit, sit.
A son next to his mom seems fine too.
No problem.
How about this.
You can support your mom a bit.
Your mom is a bit weak right now.
We younger ones can't just stand behind oldest brother.
We are the future heirs.
We have to squeeze into the middle.
Let our Hehe stand right in the middle.
Why?
Because his looks make up half of The jewel in the crown.
But he's our competitor, right?
So you can't be too far front.
Right, okay.
Kid.
You.
You seem to have a problem with this Stepmother.
What kind of relationship is this?
Jin Xiangyu.
Sigh.
I'm speechless.
Alright.
I think we should do this.
So the positions haven't really changed much.
Right?
Not much change, really.
Then that's it.
Let's change the requirements a bit.
Let's have Fifth Uncle sit alone.
And the rest of us will stand, okay?
Sure, sounds good.
Then you come over here.
Then we just have one.
Then we just... Yeah, you move to the middle.
You should still sit in the back.
Okay.
You, oldest brother, come here.
Oldest brother, come here.
It's fine.
It's the same if I'm here.
Master, why is your seniority so high?
I'm so annoyed!
I'm frail and sickly.
Can I sit on the side?
I don't want to stand anymore.
So weak.
Weak.
Too weak to function.
I'll go to the back.
I'll move to the back.
You?
The two of us together.
Although your personality is extremely flawed,
your looks are simply perfect.
I really get it.
Understood.
Your life.
What's wrong with being a little happier?
No.
I am smiling.
I'm really smiling.
I really am.
I'm genuinely smiling.
Come on.
Weak.
Alright.
And who is this?
Who is this?
This is my...
My mother.
So she has the highest seniority right now.
Right?
And her.
I'm her dad.
Does that work?
So,
So I,
We have to stick together.
A family of three grouped with another family of three.
Ditching the wife.
Come on.
The whole happy family.
Like this.
Your family portrait.
Let's do two family portraits, okay?
The two of us are a family portrait.
You two groups...
You two have nothing to do.
You two are so anxious you're farting on the sidelines.
We're meant to be.
I...
We'll fight you.
We're meant to be.
OK.
How about this?
I might as well marry Fifth Master.
You want to be his dad, fine.
How about we play the guns,
and you play the piggies.
Sure.
Let's just do it like this.
Meant to be.
Two, one.
For you to choose the murderer.
It seems like the murderers should stand in the middle.
And then it seems like...
The murderers,
Right.
Stand towards the middle.
We haven't even started recording yet.
Why do you think I'm the murderer?
I think the four of us...
We four waiters should be on the outside, on the side.
Am I a waiter too?
You're the designer.
I'm a designer now, am I?
Oh.
A cake designer!
Okay.
Then we'll just stand on the side, that works.
Then let's do this.
We... then we four waiters will act like this,
Asking this customer to order.
Right.
This is the VIP.
VIP works too.
They really are the VIPs.
Let's act a bit more like lapdogs, okay?
Don't look too cool.
It's hard not to look cool.
Yeah.
Exactly.
Let's act a bit more like lapdogs.
You're not allowed to be so elegant.
No, he's like this.
Right.
Yeah, act more like a lapdog.
Here's your drink.
Making all kinds of demands.
Okay.
Come on, three, two, one, go.
Yeah.
Then the same old rules.
Murderers stand over here.
Come on.
Murderers step up and stand here.
Don't back up either.
Brought to justice.
Let's cooperate.
I'll cooperate.
We need to bring out that gloating look while questioning him.
I don't even know who's gloating right now.
Just like this.
First of all, I want to say,
Could the two murderers squat down a bit?
Because from here, I look very...
Just squat down a bit.
Let's both squat down a bit.
Three, two, one.
This angle
really makes your face look slimmer.
What do you mean?
Plus, short people rarely use this kind of thing.
So it's our fault?
It's mostly because we're too short.
Let's interact a bit.
Be serious.
Serious interaction.
Like this.
Absorb each other's energy.
We're not using the Energy-Absorbing Art, so don't do that.
Absorb it like this.
Be a bit more normal.
We're the Six Heroes of the Martial World, okay?
Who cares what heroes we are?
Let's shoot this short video demo group by group.
Okay, so it has to be in this set, right?
Right, right.
What's the ending for this?
We're shooting the ending first, right?
We just wave at the camera.
Then I'll say 3, 2, 1.
And we all say "Happy Escape," okay?
Then, after we say "Happy Escape,"
we drop the easter egg.
OK.
Okay.
3, 2, 1.
Happy Escape!
Right.
Happy Thanksgiving.
So we wave first,
and then say "Happy Escape."
Right, right, I'll say 3, 2, 1.
Then we'll say it. Okay, let's do this.
Mr. Cui and Xiaoding,
let's lean against the sofa.
Okay.
A bit like this, right?
No problem.
That works.
Turn towards me a bit.
Right.
Turn a little bit.
Like this. Come here.
Come on.
You sit here.
Then you come here too.
Right?
Let's just do it the same way.
Can we... or maybe not, just sit here.
Rest your legs here.
Okay.
OK?
Just like this.
Will I block you?
It's fine.
You won't block me at all.
Happy Escape!
Okay, wave.
Back to the old days.
3, 2, 1.
Happy Escape!